<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pierre Haou</title>
    <link>https://pierrehaou.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pierre Haou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pierrehaou.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Quick Primer on Self-Play in Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://pierrehaou.github.io/blog/selfplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pierrehaou.github.io/blog/selfplay/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;Train tirelessly to defeat the greatest enemy, yourself, and to discover the greatest master, yourself&amp;quot;
 - Amituofo DeepMind has created AI that will crush any human player in Go, Chess, Shogi, and Starcraft 2.OpenAI has made similar strides in complex strategy games, notably in Dota 2. The agents in these games all achieved mastery using deep reinforcement learning. Yet, this is only part of the story. What was the magic sauce that sent these systems&#39; playing ability out of the atmosphere?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL) and Cooperative AI</title>
      <link>https://pierrehaou.github.io/blog/marl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pierrehaou.github.io/blog/marl/</guid>
      <description>Agents play hide and seek in OpenAI’s Emergent Tool Use from Multi-Agent Interaction. Gif by OpenAI.
Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL) is a subfield of reinforcement learning that is becoming increasingly relevant and has been blowing my mind (see gif and link above). It has found incredible success in popular strategy games and will be key to the continued advancement of several emerging technologies, communication between different autonomous vehicles being one such example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://pierrehaou.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pierrehaou.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>//Gym-Snake-MultiAgent A single and multi agent reinforcement learning environment for conducting reinforcement learning experiments. //AR Dragon Blitzkrieg //SpaceInvaders Check out some of my other projects!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://pierrehaou.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pierrehaou.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Have worn plenty of hats, currently doing a software engineering at Tableau/Salesforce this summer.
Previously:
 Software @ Better.com Strategic communications and Public Involvement @ Portland Bureau of Transportation Graduated from the University of Oregon in 2019 with a BA in Political Science Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion @ Metro (regional government in Oregon) Youth advocacy @ Immigrant and Refugee Organization  My interests:
 All things Product! reinforcement learning effective altruisim public policy (specifically its intersection with emerging technologies) transportation planning mind and body relationship NBA/Premier League  If we have mutual interests, or not, hit me up to chat!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
